<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE properties SYSTEM "http://java.sun.com/dtd/properties.dtd">
<properties version="1.0">
	<entry key="Minecraft 1.6.2">Beta 0.2.20|http://adf.ly/pTHhK</entry>
	<entry key="Minecraft 1.6.4">Beta 0.2.20|http://adf.ly/pTHhK</entry>
	<entry key="Minecraft 1.7.10">Pre 1.0.11|NO_LINK</entry>
	<entry key="Beta 0.2.06">Added a slew of NEI plugins, Force Furnaces, IC2 Force Machines, Iron Chest TileBox upgrading and the Book of Mudora.  Info: http://bit.ly/dartPost</entry>
	<entry key="Beta 0.2.07">Several bugfixes and tweaks, also added Storage Units and Forceaflouge Blocks.  Info: http://bit.ly/dartPost</entry>
	<entry key="Beta 0.2.08">More than a dozen bugfixes pertaining to Force Machines, InvTweaks support for Storage Units and Force Packs and updated to Thaumcraft 4 API.  Info: http://bit.ly/dartPost</entry>
	<entry key="Beta 0.2.09">Emergency Patch: More than a dozen bugfixes pertaining to Force Machines, InvTweaks support for Storage Units and Force Packs and updated to Thaumcraft 4 API.  Info: http://bit.ly/dartPost</entry>
	<entry key="Beta 0.2.10">Bugfixes for various Item Card interactions and a possible ThaumCrash involving golems.  More Thaumcraft aspects for DartCraft items and a way to recover 'impossible' research notes.  Info: http://bit.ly/dartPost</entry>
	<entry key="Beta 0.2.11">Bugfixes/Exploit fixes.  The Magic Meter is here - added Chu Chus and Force Potions as well.  No more unintended Infuser mooching.  Serious config options.  Info: http://bit.ly/dartPost</entry>
	<entry key="Beta 0.2.12">Bug/Crash fixes and more config options.  Mooch mode is back.  (If configured)  SS2 'support'.  Info: http://bit.ly/dartPost</entry>
	<entry key="Beta 0.2.13">Many bugfixes and even more config options.  Treasure and Spoils Bags have been reworked.  Info: http://bit.ly/dartPost</entry>
	<entry key="Beta 0.2.14">Bugfixes and config options.  Goodbye Refined Iron; hello Dart Iron!  Info: http://bit.ly/dartPost</entry>
	<entry key="Beta 0.2.15">Bugfixes and stability updates.  Added a configurable whitelist for Force Wrenchable TileEntities.  Thermal Expansion Support.  Info: http://bit.ly/dartPost</entry>
	<entry key="Beta 0.2.16">Bugfixes and config options.  Added the Time Upgrade, Throwable/Stackable Force Flasks and much more.  Changelog/videos available at: http://bit.ly/dartPost</entry>
	<entry key="Beta 0.2.17">Emergency Patch!  Fixed a possible crash on load in verbose mod packs.</entry>
	<entry key="Beta 0.2.18">Serious bugfixes and some additional config options.</entry>
	<entry key="Beta 0.2.19">Bugfixes and config options.  Force Bursting, Fairy Fountains, Bombs and Skyblock friendly features have been added.  Info: http://bit.ly/dartPost</entry>
	<entry key="Beta 0.2.20">Generation bugfix.  Hud options and in-game toggle hotkey with 6 preset locations.  (Sneak + hotkey to toggle "ZeldaHud" as well.)  Bonus UU recipes.  Info: http://bit.ly/dartPost</entry>
	<entry key="1.0.0">Initial version of Project Alchemy for Minecraft 1.7.10.  It's a brand new world!</entry>
	<entry key="Pre 1.0.11">Fixed an exploit in the Atelier.</entry>
</properties>
